Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Media Resources and Research Department Records, 1959-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Media Resources and Research Department records 1959-2000 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office.
8 linear feet Extent: 6000 Items
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The Media Resources and Research Department was responsible for media research and media planning support activities within JWT's Chicago Office. The JWT Media Resources and Research Department Records spans the years 1959-2000 and primarily includes proprietary research reports on a wide variety of topics relevant to media planning, usage and evaluation. In addition, the collection includes clippings, departmental administrative files, a U-matic videocassette; and writings and speeches of key departmental executives. Topics include general media planning and effectiveness research; studies on newspapers, magazines and other print media; broadcast and cable television viewing and television commercials; outdoor advertising research; radio advertising; video and VCR usage research; demographic research, especially on media usage among women, young people, and African Americans; and international media studies. Client-specific research includes case studies of Kodak; Kraft; The U.S. Marine Corps; and Warner-Lambert. There is also a small reference library of materials published by other research firms including A.C. Nielsen; Audit Bureau of Circulations; Daniel Starch; and Magazine Publishers Association. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
RL.00673
Language: Material in English
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
In addition, original audiovisual materials are closed to patron use. Technical Services staff need to produce use copies before contents can be accessed.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office. Media Resources and Research Department Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1993-2001.
Historical Note
Founded in 1864, the J. Walter Thompson Company (JWT) is one of the oldest and largest enduring advertising agencies in the United States. The Media Resources and Research Department was responsible for media research and media planning support activities within JWT's Chicago Office.
Collection Overview
The JWT Media Resources and Research Department Records spans the years 1959-2000 and primarily includes proprietary research reports on a wide variety of topics relevant to media planning, usage and evaluation. In addition, the collection includes clippings, departmental administrative files, a U-matic videocassette; and writings and speeches of key departmental executives. Topics include general media planning and effectiveness research; studies on newspapers, magazines and other print media; broadcast and cable television viewing and television commercials; outdoor advertising research; radio advertising; video and VCR usage research; demographic research, especially on media usage among women, young people, and African Americans; and international media studies. Client-specific research includes case studies of Kodak; Kraft; The U.S. Marine Corps; and Warner-Lambert. There is also a small reference library of materials published by other research firms including A.C. Nielsen; Audit Bureau of Circulations; Daniel Starch; and Magazine Publishers Association.
Collection Arrangement
The Collection is arranged into five Series: Administrative Files; Media; Research Reports; Audiovisual Materials; and Reference Library. Administrative Files includes clippings; policy statements; press releases; departmental overviews and mission; and writings and speeches by key departmental executives. Media includes writings and reports on media, organized by medium; Research Reports includes research on media usage and effectiveness; client-specific media case studies; demographic studies and international media research. Audiovisual Materials contains non-print-format media. The Reference Library contains research reports produced by entities other than JWT.
Subject Headings
J. Walter Thompson Company; J. Walter Thompson Company. Chicago Office; A.C. Nielsen Company; A.C. Nielsen Company. Media Research Group; Audit Bureau of Circulations; Daniel Starch and Staff; Eastman Kodak Company; Kraft Foods Company; Magazine Publishers Association; United States. Marine Corps; Warner-Lambert Company; Advertising, Magazine; Advertising, Magazine -- United States; Advertising, Newspaper; Advertising, Newspaper -- United States; Advertising, Outdoor; Advertising, Outdoor -- United States; Advertising media planning; Advertising media planning -- United States; African American consumers; African American consumers -- United States; Cable television advertising; Cable television advertising -- United States; Demographic surveys; Demographic surveys -- United States; Mass media; Mass media -- United States; Media and African Americans; Radio advertising; Radio advertising -- United States; Radio audiences; Radio audiences -- United States; Television advertising; Television advertising -- United States; Television viewers; Television viewers -- United States; Videocassette recorders; Women consumers; Women consumers -- United States; Young consumers; Young consumers -- United States; Clippings; Videocassettes; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
Related Material
Related materials may be found in the following collections of the J. Walter Thompson Company Archives:
Ronald B. Kaatz Papers
Frankfurt Office. Paul-G. Siebel Papers
Information Center Records
Publications Collection
Staff Meeting Minutes
Related materials may also be found in other collections within the Hartman Center:
Leo Bogart Papers
John Benjamin Harris Papers
McGraw-Hill Marketing Information Center Vertical File
Charles McKinney Papers
John Paver Papers
Contents of Collection
- Administrative Files, 1976-1994 and undated, (2 boxes)
  - Clippings, 1986-1987, (3 folders) (Box 1)
  - Detroit Office media changes, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Epcot presentation, 1984 (Box 1)
  - JWT budgeting philosophy, 1991 (Box 1)
  - JWT philosophy of advertising and spending, 1993 (Box 1)
  - Media Directors meeting, 1988 (Box 1)
  - Media Leadership workshop, 1984 (Box 1)
  - Media Resources and Research Department overview, 1989 and undated (Box 1)
  - Miscellaneous writings and speeches (Box 1)
    - Advertising During a Recession, 1983 (Box 1)
    - Advertising in the LBO Era, circa 1988 (Box 1)
    - Communications in the Future, by Richard Kostyra, 1991 (Box 1)
    - History of A.C. Nielsen, 1987 (Box 1)
  - North American client list, 1989 (Box 1)
  - Press releases, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 1)
  - Prodigy, 1990 (Box 1)
  - Speeches by Alice Sylvester, 1986-1994 (Box 1)
  - Speeches by Bob Warrens, 1980-1993, (2 folders) (Box 2)
  - Speeches by David Marans, 1990-1994 (Box 2)
  - Speeches by Deborah Solomon, 1987-1993 (Box 2)
  - Staff memos, 1987-1988 (Box 2)
  - T-Plan, 1976 (Box 2)
- Media, 1959-1994 and undated, (8 boxes) (Box 2)
  - General (Box 2)
    - AAAA Media Day keynote address by Don Johnston, 1981 (Box 2)
    - Changing Media Environment, Security Analysts meeting, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Electronic Media Update (newsletter), 1982-1985 (Box 2)
    - For Immediate Consideration (newsletter), 1989-1991 (Box 2)
    - In Defense of Mass Media, 1989 (Box 2)
    - International Media, 1991 (Box 2)
    - Look at U.S. Media, presentation, 1985 (Box 2)
    - Media: The New Creative Frontier, 1989 (Box 2)
    - Media Cross Ownership Directory, 1991, (2 folders) (Box 2)
    - Media Options Forum (by Ivy Hoffman), 1994 (Box 2)
    - Media panel, 1987 (Box 2)
    - Media Planning and Buying Function, presentation, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Media Planning Guide, circa 1980s, (2 folders) (Box 3)
    - Media reports, 1990 (Box 3)
    - Media reports binder, 1973-1974, (4 folders) (Box 3)
    - Media Scheduling Patterns, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Media study: Newspaper, Magazine, Outdoor, 1959, (1-2 of 3 folders) (Box 3)
    - Media study: Newspaper, Magazine, Outdoor, 1959 (continued), (3 of 3 folders) (Box 4)
    - Media systems catalog, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Media Vehicle Checklist, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Media weighting, 1984 (Box 4)
    - New media opportunities, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Pocket Guide to Media Terms and Media Math, 1984 (Box 4)
    - Sales-Effective Media Planning, circa 1990 (Box 4)
    - Trends and Projections of Media Costs, 1970-1983, 1979 (Box 4)
    - Trends and Projections of Media Costs, 1970-1985, 1982 (Box 4)
    - U.S. Consumer Media Reference, 1991, 1994, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - U.S. Consumer Media Review, 1987-1990, (3 folders) (Box 4)
    - U.S. Media Resources and Research, 1985 (Box 4)
  - Print--Magazines (Box 4)
    - Baby magazine study, 1987 (Box 4)
    - Beyond the Numbers: Factors Affecting Magazine Ad Performance (Leo Burnett Co. report), 1978 (Box 4)
    - Demographic and Geographic Editions, 1989 (Box 4)
    - How Magazines Are Measured, undated (Box 4)
    - How To Evaluate Magazine Subscriber Studies, 1986 and undated (Box 4)
    - Magazine Ad Positioning, 1983 and 1991, (2 folders) (Box 4)
    - Magazine Ad Size Effectiveness, 1983 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Audience Adjustments, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Executional Variables, 1991 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Inserts, 1989 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Merchandising Opportunities, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Planning Models, circa 1981 (Box 4)
    - Magazine Regional Advertising Opportunities, 1988 (Box 4)
    - Multiple Ad Pages in a Magazine, 1986 (Box 5)
    - One After the Other, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Perspective on SMRB Syndicated Magazine Audience Research, 1985 (Box 5)
    - Print for the Baby Carriage Trade, 1987 (Box 5)
    - Report on Magazines, 1972 (Box 5)
    - Seven Sisters Meet the 90s, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Seven Sisters Revisited, circa 1986 (Box 5)
    - Special Interest Magazine Guide, 1984 (Box 5)
    - Unmeasured Magazines, 1989 (Box 5)
  - Print--Miscellaneous (Box 5)
    - Color Advertising in Newspapers, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Couponing in Magazines and Newspapers, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Print Capsules (newsletter), 1987-1993 (Box 5)
    - Report on Newspapers, circa 1973 (Box 5)
    - Simmons Business Management Readership Study, comments, 1986 (Box 5)
    - Ways of Measuring Print, 1994 (Box 5)
  - Radio (Box 5)
    - All About Radio, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Radio Format Trends for the 1980s, 1983 (Box 5)
    - Report on Radio, 1972 (Box 5)
  - Television--General (Box 5)
    - 1989/90 New Television Season Preview, 1989 (Box 5)
    - All About VPH (viewers per household), 1990 (Box 5)
    - Barter Syndication Update, 1989 (Box 5)
    - Captive Audience TV, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Expanding Marketplace Intelligence, 1990 (Box 5)
    - Flighting vs. Continuity in TV Scheduling, undated (Box 5)
    - Football--What Did Happen, What Will Happen, 1993 (Box 5)
    - High Definition Television: TV's Next Generation, 1988 (Box 5)
    - JWT's View of Interactive Television Environment, 1993 (Box 5)
    - Likeability study, 1985-1991 (Box 6)
    - Clutter and the TV Environment, 1984 (Box 6)
    - Nielsen Report on HUT/PUT Trends, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Out of Home Viewing, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Predicting the Useful Future, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Report on Television, 1973 (Box 6)
    - Reports on TV Viewing, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Rites of March, 1989 (Box 6)
    - SMRB and MRI Viewing Data, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Sports Reach Manual, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Television Audience Measurement, 1990 (Box 6)
    - Television Segment Ratings, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 6)
    - TV Fact Book, 1988-1992 (Box 6)
    - TVReach: The New TV Reach and Frequency System, manual, 1989 (Box 6)
    - TVReach and Mixit manual, 1991 (Box 6)
    - Viewing in the Distracted Environment, 1991 (Box 6)
  - Television--Cable (Box 6)
    - Cable Capsules, 1982-1988, (5 folders) (Box 6)
    - Cable Networks Viewership, 1989 (Box 6)
    - Cable Operators Program Interests, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Home Shopping, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Is Advertising in Pay-TV's Future?, 1987 (Box 6)
    - Local Market Ratings for National Cable Networks, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Must-Carry Negotiations Continue, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Pocket Guide to Cable Communications, 1981-1986 (Box 7)
    - Review of Cable, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Status Report on CATV, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Ted Bates' Superstation Study, comments, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Update on the Fox Network, 1989 (Box 7)
    - World of Local Cable, 1989 (Box 7)
  - Television--Commercials (Box 7)
    - 10 Second Commercials Perspective, circa 1982 (Box 7)
    - 15-Second Commercials, 1981-1986, (2 folders) (Box 7)
    - 60 Seconds News and Reviews (newsletter), 1985-1989 (Box 7)
    - 1992 Television Commercial Monitoring Report, 1992 (Box 7)
    - Advertorials and Infomercials, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Commercial wearout, 1967-1981 and undated (Box 7)
    - Commercial Zapping, 1984 (Box 7)
    - Creative Uprising, circa 1987 (Box 7)
    - Day After Recall, 1982 (Box 7)
    - Fifteen-Second Commercials: The Simple Truth, 1984 (Box 7)
    - How Much Do Remote Control Devices Increase Flipping?, 1987 (Box 7)
    - Infomercials: A JWT Perspective, 1993 (Box 7)
    - IRI Zapping Study, 1984 (Box 7)
    - J.Walter 15s: What Now?, 1986 (Box 7)
    - Look at 15-Second Commercials in 1994, 1994 (Box 7)
    - Look at 15-Second Commercials in the 90s, 1990 (Box 7)
    - Million Dollar Minute, 1985 (Box 7)
    - On-Air Persuasiveness: Memorability of 15-Second Commercials, undated (Box 7)
    - Qualitative Study of Commercial Avoidance, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Quality vs. Quantity, undated (Box 7)
    - Shorter Units, 1985 (Box 7)
    - Split :30s: The Long and Short of It, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Spot TV Measurement, by Jon Marks, 1992 (Box 8)
    - Television Commercials: Position in a Pod, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Three Sides to Shorter Units, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Trends in 15-Second Commercials on Network TV, 1986-1994, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - TV Commercials: In-Program vs. Between Programs, 1991 (Box 8)
    - Update on 15-Second Commercials, 1993 (Box 8)
  - Television--Network (Box 8)
    - 1988 Summer Olympics, 1988 (Box 8)
    - 3 Network New Season Report, 1984 (Box 8)
    - All About Network Clearances, 1988-1989, (3 folders) (Box 8)
    - NBC Prime Time Fall, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Network Sports, 1st Edition, 1984 (Box 8)
    - Network Sports Auto Racing, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Network Sports Basketball, 1986 (Box 8)
    - Prime Time Soap Trends, 1985 (Box 8)
    - Primetime TV Schedule, 1985-1986, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Shogun studies, 1980, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Thoughts on Network TV Pricing, 1986 (Box 9)
  - Video and VCRs (Box 9)
    - Country Store Reborn, 1985 (Box 9)
    - Predictions, 1991 (Box 9)
    - VCR: The New Star in the Media Galaxy, 1988 (Box 9)
    - VCR Measurement, 1987 (Box 9)
    - VCR Status, 1982 (Box 9)
    - VCRs: Then and Now, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Video in the Eye of the Viewer, 1985 (Box 9)
- Research Reports, 1970-2000 and undated, (5 boxes) (Box 9)
  - General (Box 9)
    - 237 Key Trends, 1989 (Box 9)
    - Advertising and Sales Promotion Report, 1987 (Box 9)
    - Advertising Frequency and Scheduling Strategies (Leo Burnett Co. report), 1979 (Box 9)
    - Advertising's Impact on Sales, 1988 (Box 9)
    - Annual Advertising Expenditures, 1991 (Box 9)
    - ARF Copy Research Validity Study, 1990 (Box 9)
    - Attention Levels to Advertising, 1986 (Box 9)
    - Bridging the I-Way, 1994 (Box 9)
    - Consumer Panel, 1987, (2 folders) (Box 9)
    - Couponing and Promotion Trends, 1988-1991 (Box 9)
    - Examination of Order Bias (in survey questions), undated (Box 9)
    - Flighting articles, 1973-1980 and undated (Box 9)
    - How Advertising Works, 1991 (Box 10)
    - It's a Long Way Down to the Creative Department, 1986 (Box 10)
    - JWT Research Conference, 1978, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Leveraging Effect Report, 1991 (Box 10)
    - Magazine/Television Effectiveness, 1970 (Box 10)
    - Market Modeling, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Marketing Information in Transition, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Media Habits of Top Level Executives, 1986 (Box 10)
    - Media Mix Reach and Frequency, 1978 (Box 10)
    - News and Reviews from Media Resources and Research (newsletter), 1985-1989 (Box 10)
    - NPD Brand Loyalty Study, 1992 (Box 10)
    - Products as Props in Movies and TV, 1989 (Box 10)
    - Recent Trends in Couponing, 1986-1987, (2 folders) (Box 10)
    - Report on Outdoor Advertising, 1972 (Box 10)
    - Ron Kaatz original research projects, 1981-1984 (Box 10)
    - Searching for the Answers..., 1984 (Box 10)
    - Shape of the Advertising Response Function, by Julian Simon and Johan Arndt, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Single Source Data, 1987 (Box 10)
    - Sliding Schedule of Advertising Weight, 1980 (Box 10)
    - Study of Top Level Executives' Media Habits, 1988 (Box 10)
    - Summary of 1976 Research and Development, 1977, (3 folders) (Box 11)
    - Task Force Report: Non-Print Communications, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Tough Questions about Single Source Data, by Alice Sylvester, undated (Box 11)
    - Volumetric Data in Syndicated Research, 1985 (Box 11)
    - What We Learned, What We Did Right, and What Needs Improvement on the People-Meter System, by Alice Sylvester, 1988 (Box 11)
    - What's Happening in Media Research?, 1991 (Box 11)
    - Year One of the People Meter, 1988 (Box 11)
  - Client-Specific (Box 11)
    - Chinese Food Brand, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Kellogg's Nutri-Grain, 1981 (Box 11)
    - Kodak media research meeting, 1983 (Box 11)
    - Kraft Network TV (Nielsen Index), 1986, (2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Kraft Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese, 1979-1984, (1 of 2 folders) (Box 11)
    - Kraft Philadelphia Brand Cream Cheese, 1979-1984 (continued), (2 of 2 folders) (Box 12)
    - Kraft Singles, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Media and the Marine Corps, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Northwest Airlines Shuttle media pitch, 1991 (Box 12)
    - Personal Touch, 1985 (Box 12)
    - S.C. Johnson, Glade Spinfresh, 1983-1984 (Box 12)
    - Warner-Lambert communication satellite systems, 1982 (Box 12)
  - Demographic (Box 12)
    - Advertising and Black America, 1974 (Box 12)
    - Advertising to Women, 1974 (Box 12)
    - America: Outsiders Looking In (Ogilvy & Mather report), 1989 (Box 12)
    - Children's Print Media Opportunities, 1989 (Box 12)
    - It's Not How Old You Are, It's How You Live, 1989 (Box 12)
    - Media Usage Among Black Americans, 1992 (Box 12)
    - Media Usage Among Males 16-19, 1990 (Box 12)
    - Persons 12-24 Media Guide, circa 1990 (Box 12)
    - TV Viewing Among Non-Whites and Whites (Nielsen Index), 1991 (Box 12)
    - TV Viewing in Black and All Other Households (Nielsen Index), 1991 (Box 12)
    - Womenscope, 1985 (Box 12)
  - International (Box 12)
    - France and Italy, 1980 and undated (Box 12)
    - Hong Kong Population, 1984 (Box 12)
    - International Media Spreadsheet, 1992 (Box 12)
    - International Media Spreadsheet--Europe, undated (Box 12)
    - Media Mix--Report on International Studies, 1992 (Box 12)
    - New Zealand Marketing Trends, 1984-1985 (Box 12)
    - Puerto Rico Media Profile, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Switzerland as a Market, 1985 (Box 13)
  - Reference Resources (Box 13)
    - Guide to Local Market Sources, 1990 (Box 13)
    - Guide to Media Research Sources, 1987 (Box 13)
    - JWT Catalog of Media Research Reports and Studies, undated (Box 13)
    - Leo Burnett Advertising and Media Fact Book, 1994 (Box 13)
    - Market Research Publications List, 1989 (Box 13)
    - Media Research Tool Box, by Deborah Solomon, undated (Box 13)
    - Test Marketing Guide Book, 1988, (2 folders) (Box 13)
  - Research Systems and Tools (Box 13)
    - Cluster Plus vs. Prizm, 1984 (Box 13)
    - DYG Scan: A Trend Identification Program, 2000 (Box 13)
    - People Meter, 1988 (Box 13)
    - Perspectives on People Meters, Commercial Modeling and Qualitative Rating Systems, 1985 (Box 13)
    - RF Comp User Research Manual, 1971 (Box 13)
    - Single Source/Scanner Systems, 1987-1991 (Box 13)
    - So You Think You Want a Qualitative Rating Service?, by Jamie Cunning, 1992 (Box 13)
    - Using Adspender, undated (Box 13)
- Audiovisual Materials, 1977, (1 box) (Box 13)
  - The Concept of Effective Reach (JWT Learning Series). 1977. 25 minutes running time. Format: Umatic. (Box 14)
- Reference Library, 1965-1998, (4 boxes) (Box 14)
  - A.C. Nielsen (Box 14)
    - Coming Revolution in Television Measurement Research, 1987 (Box 15)
    - Daytime TV '70, 1970 (Box 15)
    - Holiday Viewing Report 1980-81 and 1993-94, 1995 (Box 15)
    - Holiday Television Viewing, 1982 (Box 15)
    - Network TV Mini-Series, 1985 (Box 15)
    - Report on Television, 1989-1998 (Box 15)
    - Television Audience, 1975-1984 (Box 15)
    - Television Audience (continued), 1985-1994 (Box 16)
    - Television Viewing Among Blacks, 1985-1990 (Box 16)
    - Television Viewing Among Whites and Non-Whites, 1979-1984 (Box 16)
    - Television Viewing at Christmas and New Years, 1977 (Box 16)
    - Television Viewing in Non-White and White Households, 1973 (Box 16)
    - Television Viewing on Memorial and Independence Day, 1977-1978 (Box 17)
    - Television Viewing on Thanksgiving, 1975 (Box 17)
    - Television Viewing to Network News Programming, 1984 (Box 17)
    - Weekday Daytime Audience, 1965 (Box 17)
    - Weekday Daytime TV, 1975, 1980, 1984 (Box 17)
    - What TV Ratings Really Mean, 1987, 1995 (Box 17)
  - American Market Research Bureau (AMRB) (Box 17)
    - Measuring the Audience of Magazines, 1972 (Box 17)
  - Arbitron (Box 17)
    - Radio Today, 1991 (Box 17)
  - Audit Bureau of Circulations (ABC) (Box 17)
    - Integrity in a Changing World, by Charles O. Bennett, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Magazine Trend Report, 1981 (Box 17)
  - Audits and Surveys, Inc. (Box 17)
    - Readership of Ten Major Magazines, 1975 (Box 17)
  - CableTelevision Advertising Bureau (CAB) (Box 17)
    - Cable Network Profiles, 1993 (Box 17)
    - Cable TV Facts, 1992-1994 (Box 17)
  - Daniel Starch and Staff (Box 17)
    - Demographics, 1969 (Box 17)
  - Donnelly Marketing Information Services (Box 17)
    - ClusterPLUS Description Guide, 1992 (Box 17)
  - HRP Programming (Box 17)
    - Network and Syndication Overview, 1993 (Box 18)
  - Magazine Publishers Association (MPA) (Box 18)
    - Advertising Impact of Magazines in Conjunction with Television, 1990 (Box 18)
    - Magazine Almanac, 1988 (Box 18)
    - Magazine Handbook, 1990-1991 (Box 18)
  - Northwestern University School of Journalism (Box 18)
    - Journal of Media Planning, 1986-1991 (Box 18)
  - Ogilvy Center for Research and Development (Box 18)
    - Attitude Change: Making It Stick, 1989 (Box 18)
  - W.R. Simmons and Associates Research Inc. (Box 18)
    - Selective Markets and the Media Reaching Them, 1967-1968 (Box 18)